<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pedro's Blog</title><link>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Pedro's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A discussion about Fatherhood and kids</title><link>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/iamafather/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/iamafather/</guid><description>First a Disclaimer here: I do respect and find it legitimate the decision of People that do not want to have kids I understand that kids can sometimes be inconvenient for some living standards (they are noisy, cannot regulate themselves easily) Saying that lets go to the text&amp;hellip;
Kids are also People I was living my life as usual, when suddenly I bumped into this message on a whatsapp group</description></item><item><title>Reading Pragmatic Programmer - Part 2</title><link>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/pragprog2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:41:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/pragprog2/</guid><description>New points for the book Throughout the book there are some Challenges proposed to the reader as well as exercises to to practice some concepts learned through the book.
There is also Tips that translates the ideas of each one the sections. There are some really useful tips like this one.
Chapter 1, 2 and 3&amp;hellip; These chapters were a very nice beginning for this adventure and left me already with a lot to think, and most important, to do!</description></item><item><title>Reading Pragmatic Programmer</title><link>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/pragprog1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 10:41:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/pragprog1/</guid><description>It was already time! I had a copy of the Pragmatic Programmer, in a PDF shitty format. And that was my excuse to no read it.
I have always been keen of the philosoy to credit people for their work. I understand that in Brazil leisure is not that accessible as in other places in the world so I don&amp;rsquo;t blame people buying recorded movies from cinemas. I understand the struggle.</description></item><item><title>I will continue to study Elixir</title><link>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/iwillcontinuestudyingelixir/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 21:48:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/iwillcontinuestudyingelixir/</guid><description>I took part in a selection process in a company that I was really interested in working with.
The process till the last interview was smooth and pretty nice. The end I was a little bit frustrated because was not selected to continue in the process but in the end it was very important for me in a way and I will explain why.
Prologue I think it is important to point out that I am a Quereinsteiger and came from the chemical Engineering area, so I am probably not the profile you search if you want someone with fluent IT theoretical and algorithmy knowledge.</description></item><item><title>Like HSM teached us, 'This is me'</title><link>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/startpost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 14:53:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/posts/startpost/</guid><description>Introduction It is pretty hard to start a text to talk about yourself, even more difficult is to write an introduction about atext that talk about yourself, but let&amp;rsquo;s do it! 😎
This text will containt what made me come to where I am right now. This is merely an selfanalysis that I decided to transform in a Blog Post.
So if you like long stories, you are welcome to read through it!</description></item><item><title/><link>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/books/books_list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://pedrocecchetti.github.io/books/books_list/</guid><description>Books This will be a list of books I read each year. Before 2024 will be what I can remember from old books I read. Maybe in the future I can also make some critics and comments but for now we have the links and names
2024 Title Type Language Rating Harry Potter und die Kammer des Schreckens Fantasy DE-de ⭐⭐⭐ Glauben Sie an die Wahrheit Comic DE-de ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Harry Potter und der Gefangene von Azkaban- Fantasy DE-de ⭐⭐⭐ Der ZeitRaum Comic DE-de ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ 1984 Comic PT-br ⭐⭐⭐⭐ Von Unten Comic DE-de/EN ⭐⭐⭐ The last Goodbye Thriller EN-en ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Nowhere Girl Comic EN-en ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ 2023 Title Type Language Rating Salvar o fogo Romance PT-br ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Hearthstopper Comic PT-br ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Pragmatic Programmer Comic PT-br ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ 2022 Title Type Language Rating Torto Arado Romance Portuguese BR ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Fluent Python Tech English ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐</description></item></channel></rss>